that's about value creating role for
insurance and that's something that
corporates would value much more than
just saying that you have your risk
Transfer Partner
so that's a journey that we started back
in 2014 and part of the journey we
started the Indian business management
award to recognize and
our feeling was that in India you see
awards for you know business you see
award for leadership you see awards for
financial performance but you never had
award for uh you know good risk
management strategy so that was the
thought process behind the Indian dress
particular Awards which we will have
today in the evening
was
yes respiration is important we all
understand that and I think the last you
know the point she made last three years
have really taught us that lesson uh you
know across the world
but the feedback that we were getting
was that you know Wireless management is
important how do we quantify you know
what we're doing is there some way to
figure out
uh or build an index that tells us where
we stand uh within the industry or
across Industries
now this is not easy because risk is not
just the type of risk that we covered if
you look at a business there's a
multiple risks that you have to look at
and maybe there are models and entices
that looks at Predators there are models
and realizes that looks at uh you know
operational risk but at least we didn't
see across the world too many
comprehensive Risk Index that defect
would be useful to look at you know
overall businesses
when he spoke to them they had a concept
that we jointly evolved and then we
worked together to you know launch this
Index this is the third year uh you know
this is going to talk about the the
findings I'll not get into that that's
his domain but we are really happy to
partner with them and provide this tool
for Indian corporates
the launch of the index or the or the
the results of the study this year is
not the ending itself in the whole Focus
for us is that how do we help Indian
corporates with these inputs uh you know
become even better in their risk
management approach that's the thought
process but you know as always there's
all you know the way to start it is to
launch the index that's what we're here
for and from Isis and robots side that
we again welcome all of you uh we thank
you for joining us and look forward to
having a nice